Preliminary Guide to the AIDS Action Foundation records, 1984-2006 MS2212
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ryan White Care Act and Ryan White Foundation, 1990-2005; Series 4; 7.5 Linear Feet
  - Legislation for the act, 1990-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - Ryan White Title II Information, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - RW Title II supplemental grant proposed, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - RW Title V AIDS Dental Reimbursement, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Ryan White Foundation, 1993-1998; Series 4 Subseries 3
    In 1992, Ryan White's mother, Jeanne, founded the national nonprofit Ryan White Foundation. The foundation worked to increase awareness of HIV/AIDS-related issues, with a focus on hemophiliacs like Ryan White, and on families caring for relatives with the disease. The foundation was active throughout the 1990s. In 2000, Jeanne White closed the foundation and merged its remaining assets with AIDS Action.
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, Circa 1993-1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 64)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, Circa 1993-1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 65)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1993, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, Circa 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White Foundation incoming letters, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Drawings, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 87)
      General note
      These are drawings done by children related to the Ryan White Foundation and award from Video Industry Aids Action Committee -VIAAC Visionary given to Aids Action in 2002.
    - Drawings, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 88)
      These are drawings done by children related to the Ryan White Foundation.
    - Drawings, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 89)
- Legislation, 1996-2005; Series 5; 3.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains records related to various pieces of legislation that AIDS Action has been involved with including the Coburn HIV Prevention Bill, and many aspects of appropriations funding for different agencies and nonprofits involved with the fight against AIDS. The material dates from 1996-2005.
  - Funding info by state FY96, 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - FY96 research approps., 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations FY96 House testimony, 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Appropriations FY 96 Pres. Budget Req., 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Appropriations FY96 96 budget process, 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - FY96 Ryan White funding, 1996; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Voting record information, 1996; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Vote count key, 1996 July; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 104th Congress voting records, 1996; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Coburn HIV Prevention, 1997-1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - HIV treatment improvement act of 1997, Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - 105th: HIV Prevention Act 1997 (Coburn), Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - HIV Prevention Act of 1997 Coburn Bill, Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - FY 97 Advocacy materials, 1997; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - FY97 L/HHS approps- House, 1997; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - FY97 L/HHS Approps. Final, 1997; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - HOPWA FY 97 Approps, 1997; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - FY97 Labor, Health and Human Services Education and related agencies summary, 1997; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - FY97 L/HHS Approps. Senate, 1997; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - CDC funds to state and local health department's public health agencies for FY97, 1997; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Federal appropriations, 1998; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Work incentives improvement act of 1998 S1858, Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 3206 Amend the Fair Housing Act of 1998, Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - President's FY'98 Bud. Ltr., 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - FY98 Pres. Budget/Admin. Testimony, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - FY98 Budget and Resolution, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - FY98 L/HHS Approps Senate, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - FY98 VA/HUD Approps. Senate, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - FY98 Funding HIV/AIDS Prevention Chairman, L/HHS, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - FY98 L/HHS Approps House, 1998; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - FY 98 President's budget, 1998; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Appropriations FY98, 1998; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - FY 98 Budget, 1998; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Speech by Congressman Gaske, 1998 March 31; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Dear colleagues letters for appropriations, 1998; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - FY 2004 Budget, 2003-2004; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - FY2004 Approps book, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Approps book FY 2005, 2004; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - FY 2005 Budget, 2004-2005; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 105th House and Senate, undated; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - 105th Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 3717 Fed. Funding NEP, undated; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 2409-S. 1147 The Subs. Abuse Treatment Parity Act, undated; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - National AIDS Strategy, undated; Series 5 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 105th Congress new members, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - House letters 105th, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Nominations of Dr. Satcher, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - House Q and A on gift rules, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Constorium for citizens with disabilities letter Chairman of labor committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - 105th H. Res. 539 HIV Surveillance, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - HIV undate Congressman Tom Coburn, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Tiahrt Amendment, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - S1959 NEP Bill, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - 105th Congress apps., undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - HIV anti-body testing, undated; Series 5 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Voting records, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - 104th voting record, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - voting record 104th Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Senate- 103rd, 2nd Session, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - House - 103rd, 1st Session, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Voting record 102nd, 103rd Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Senate votes 103rd, 2nd Session, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Votes, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - 102 Voting records, 2nd Session, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Vote Count record - 1st Session: 104th Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - 104th Congress voting record, undated; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Vote count record pending inputs, undated; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Voting record 104th Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Voting on H.R. 3717, undated; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Voting record 104th Congress, undated; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Gregg Amendment / Mandatory Testing, undated; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Coburn HIV Prevention, undated; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Newspaper articles and other press, 1987-1998; Series 6; 3 Linear Feet
  Organized into 2 subseries: Newspaper articles and other press and Press releases and statements.
  This series contains newspaper articles, press releases, and press statements. These records date from 1987-1998.
  - Newspaper articles about AIDS Action, 1987-1998; Series 5 Subseries 1
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/3], 1987 September - 1994 July; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/3], 1987 September - 1994 July; 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/3], 1987 September - 1994 July; 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/3], 1994 July - 1994 September; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/3], 1994 July - 1994 September; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/3], 1994 July - 1994 September; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/4], 1994 October - 1995 January; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/4], 1994 October - 1995 January; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/4], 1994 October - 1995 January; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [4/4], 1994 October - 1995 January; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/4], 1995 February - 1995 April; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/4], 1995 February - 1995 April; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/4], 1995 February - 1995 April; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [4/4], 1995 February - 1995 April; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Clips mentioning AIDS Action [1/4], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Clips mentioning AIDS Action [2/4], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Clips mentioning AIDS Action [3/4], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Clips mentioning AIDS Action [4/4], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/3], 1996 March 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/3], 1996 March 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/3], 1996 March 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/2], 1996 March 16 - 1996 May 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/2], 1996 March 16 - 1996 May 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/3]], 1996 June 1 - 1996 August 30; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/3], 1996 June 1 - 1996 August 30; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/3], 1996 June 1 - 1996 August 30; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/3], 1996 September 1 - 1997 February 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/3], 1996 September 1 - 1997 February 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/3], 1996 September 1 - 1997 February 15; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/4], 1996 December 1 - 1996 March 14; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/4], 1996 December 1 - 1996 March 14; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/4], 1996 December 1 - 1996 March 14; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [4/4], 1996 December 1 - 1996 March 14; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/2], 1997; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/2], 1997; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [1/4], 1997 February 16 - 1997 March 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [2/4], 1997 February 16 - 1997 March 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [3/4], 1997 February 16 - 1997 March 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings mentioning AIDS Action [4/4], 1997 February 16 - 1997 March 31; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action clips, 1999 January 5- April 13; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Action clips, 1998 October 13 - December 14; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action clips, 1998 September 9 - October 12; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Articles, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Press releases and statements, 1994-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2
    - Press releases and statements [3/3], 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Press releases and statements [1/2], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Press releases and statements [2/2], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Press releases and statements [1/3], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Press releases and statements [2/3], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Press releases and statements [3/3], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Action Council press releases and statements, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Action Workplans [1/2], 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Action Workplans [2/2], 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations recommendations, 1993-2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Press releases and statements [1/3], 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Press releases and statements [2/3], 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Council press releases and statements, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Council press releases and statements, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Press releases and statements, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Press A-List, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Graphics, 1987-1999; Series 7; 3 Linear Feet
  This series contains photographs and negatives primarily of AIDS Action events. These images date from 1987-1999.
  - Photographs FDA Protest ACT UP Rockville, MD, 1987 October; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Photographs AIDS Protest White House, 1988; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Photographs 1989 Events World AIDS Day, Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Photograph Princess Diana, 1990 October 5; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Photographs National Leadership Awards, 1991; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Photographs Matcher Testimony, 1991 May 8; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Photographs Protest on 10th anniversary of 1st CDC report on AIDS Death, 1991 June 5; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Photographs 10 yr. anniversary of Epidemic AAC's press conference, 1991; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Photographs New Year's Eve, 1992; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Photographs AIDS Watch, 1992; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Photographs Awards, 1992; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Photographs AIDS Action Conference, 1992 September 2; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Photographs Vaccine conference, 1993 October 17; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Photographs Skills building conference New Orleans, 1993 October; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Photographs Congressional briefing on AIDS for Freshman Congressmen, early 1993; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Photographs Inaugural Open House, 1993 January; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Photographs IRA Magaziner speaks at AIDS Action Board meeting, Fall 1993; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Photographs Gebbie reception, 1993 August 2; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Photographs Open House March on D.C., 1993 April 23; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Watch, 1993; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Photographs AIDS and the caregiver featuring Herb Perry (tv show), 1993 June; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Photographs Regional Transition mtgs in 25 communities (Santa Fe), 1993; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Photographs MASH, 1994 July 24; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Photographs AIDS Action at skills building conference 1994 Atlanta, Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Photographs Satcher meeting, 1994; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Photographs AIDS Watch, 1994; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Photographs AIDS Watch, 1995; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Photographs AIDS Action briefing for White House Conference on HIV/AIDs, 1995 December; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Photographs AIDS Action Advocate New York Dinner, 1996 October 29; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Photographs National Leadership Awards, 1996; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Photographs Press Conference Medicaid, 1996 June 4; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Photographs Remember Them With Your Vote, 1996 October; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Photographs Hands Around the Capitol, 1996 October; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Photographs AIDS Events (walk, ride, dance), 1996; Series 7 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Photographs Quilt Weekend, 1996; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Photographs State of AIDS Forum, 1997 July 14; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Photographs PPC, 1997 February; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Photographs AIDS Action Regional Conference Miami, FL, 1997 March 26; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Photographs AIDS Action mtg. with Luc Montagnier and AIDS Leadership, 1997 May 14; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Photographs meeting re: Medicaid Expansion Program, 1997; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Photographs Fashion Show L.A., 1997; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Photographs Board Meeting with new Dir. Of National AIDS Policy Sandy Thurman, 1997 April 9; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Slides New York Event slide show, 1997; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Photographs National Leadership Awards, 1997; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Photographs 1997 annual reports, Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Photographs Office of National AIDS Policy reception, 1998 December 5; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Photographs Board Meeting, Spring 1998; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Photographs 1998Awards Night, Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Photographs Congressional Breakfast, 1998; Series 7 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Photographs New York City Benefit, 1998; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 1)